Dusa Praharshnand

My Contact

☑ dusapraharsh123@gmail.com

https://dusa-praharsh.vercel.app/

https://www.linkedin.com/in/dusa-praharsh/ Hyderabad, India 500020

+91 9705783228 https://github.com/DusaPraharsh

Professional Summary

I'm a self-taught developer with almost 2 years of experience across multiple streams such as Front-end, Blockchain and Game development. I believe the skill sets I possess would help me acquire exposure, experience and sharpen my skills amidst your organization's work culture.

Education

Avanthi Degree and PG College - BSc Computer Science - September 2019 -- July 2022 80% Aggregate

Narayana Junior College - MPC - July 2017 -- July 2019 71% Aggregate

Work Experience

Travel | Exploring Technologies |

Crypto and NFT Trading

Internship as Unity / Blockchain Developer at Kanine Klans - October 2023 -- Current Unity | C# | Solidity

Solidity Developer at Vivin Software - April 2023 -- August 2023 Solidity | Hardhat | Git

Freelance Front-end Developer at Hostwire Systems - February 2023 -- April 2023 React I JSX

Computing Skills	Achievements	Projects
Javascript React	1st in Eth For All Hackathon, Hyderabad, India	PayStream (Unofficial) Pay as you stream application
Solidity Hardhat Threejs Blender	Runner up at Web3 Conf India' 23, Goa, India	Javascript React Solidity
Unity C#		SupplyX (Unofficial)
Git Github		Application which integrates workflow of Manufacturers,
Interests		Retailers and Customers using Blockchain
Gaming Web Development		Javascript React Solidity